

# **ABDULLAH RAHIN**

WEB DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

# **ABOUT ME**

Hello, I am Rahin. I am a hard-working and passionate web designer and web developer with 2+ years of experience. I am highly focused on my work and completed each project as per the given schedule.believe in learning and developing new skills every day to have a successful future ahead. My main intent is to pleasure the client with my efficiency & efforts, and keep a positive rapport throughout the projects and the connection.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Web Designer & Developer at Upwork & Fiverr 2021 - Present

I am working in Upwork & Fiverr as a Web Designer & Developer with expertise in WordPress, JavaScript and PHP, and also done many local clients' projects.

WordPress & Laravel Developer

2022 - 2023

I'm worked with a team. From there I'm constantly working as a skilled web developer with a new experience.

## **CONTACT**

+88 018874-97149

🋖 Mirpur-14, Dhaka

https://aarahin.com/resume

## **EDUCATION**

2019 - 2021 Higher Secondary School Certificate (H.S.C)

Feni Collage

2021 - Present Bachelor's of Business Studies (BBS)

Dhaka Mirpur College

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS, CSS3
- Bootstrap
- WordPress
- Elementor | Divi
- Woo-commerce
- JavaScript (ES6)

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

### Full-stack Web Development

Shikbe Shobai

I completed my full-stack web development .through this course, I got familiar with web technology. I made myself proficient in HTML, CSS, WordPress, Javascript, and PHP.

#### PHP & Laravel (running)

Shikbe Shobai

For strong backend knowledge, and to make myself more efficient in PHP & most popular framework Laravel, I doing complete that course.

### **WordPress Development**

Codeman BD

I developed myself as a good wordpress developer through this course.

- JQuery
- Wix
- PSD / XD / Figma Conversion
- WordPress Theme Development
- PHP
- Laravel
- MySQL
- Version Control: Git, GitHub
- Problem-Solving & Debbuging
- Microsoft Office
- Language: English (fluent)

## **REFERENCE**

#### FAISAL HAMID HIMEL

Mentor, Shikbe Shobai +01715-234605 faisal.hamid.hemel.1992@gmail.com

#### GAZI WAFA

Mentor, Shikbe Shobai +01814-294661 gaziwafa65@gmail.com